I’m sick of saying bru, bru!
Aww that’s brisk
P-H-PHRESH
Fre- What?
Fresh.
Alright where are we boys?
New Zlun bru
nEW zeLUn
We’re going to get a car, So we can drive
Shit what kind of car?
A Toyota Corolla And hopefully they dont fuck us over
And give us a shit box, That won’t run
We’re so gonna get fucked over, Aren’t we Wally?
Yep
I feel like we’re actually gonna get fucked over
This is so fuckin nice
Push button nig-ntion
(uneasey chortle)
Woah this is fuckin smooth dude
I FEEL small dude
Its a fuckin huge car dude. Its so nice to drive
You don't even understand
YOU DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND
This is so nice to drive
WE FOUND MACDONALDS
That's really what's important?
I’m so fuckin hungry though
No green P’s No P plates! What?! Amazing
We’re fully fledged drivers
Look at the maccas, it’s so different
It’s the exact same. It’s literally the EXACT same
Also why does everyone in this country have a
kiwi accent? Have you noticed?
Ha-have n-no? Guys?
Sorry about the wait their
That’s alright, i’m happy about it
Are you kidding me right now?
Wally’s gone in the complete opposite direction
But you know what.. He’s happy.
He’s gone for a swim~
(Seductive stirring)
Do you see that chip? On the car?
Do you see the chip? The big chip?
Th-the chip Chipped on the.. Brand new car, 700 K’s man we..
Chip. Ah
Chip... Woo!
Fuck you im an annoying cunt
I’m just gonna cut out my actual asking and
Im just gonna have you saying that
Fuck you
See how he gets out
It shouldn’t be too hard, it looks aight
Pivot. Pivot!
(Swinging Erotically)
Go. Go sunburn boy
Woo, that’s fast
1.. 2..? Naw
Here he goes! 1..
That was like a synchronized skip-
Aw Awww that’s 5!
It’s 5!
Good fricken times, good fricken times
Look at the duckies and the babies
OH MY
Aw my god
Wa-wa. Hehe. Hello!
Aw you guys are pretty cute UwU
(Wheezing and chuckles)
Oh- one fell over!
(Maternal exhale)
(Wet Fart)
What’d you just do?
I’m not saying!
No come on
Go away
What’d he do Sam?
Farted as they were.. Coming down the steps
Walking right past some poor. Poor lady
What’d we do?
We just walked a long way, without water
Basically so i’m thirsty.
Ow Fuck. Ow FUCK
Dude can you just drive, not in the sun?
That’d be great thankyou
Can you just Drift all the way there?
Keep fuckin front of the car on the right side-
(Windy Orgasm)
This feels so much better
(Sobbing) It burns
Ugh made it, go go drive!
What was it, sir.. Something hostel..
In Queenstown!
Ok!
Plan is we’re hoping to find some pizza tonight
For dinner and might go to the movies after that
Then tomorrow.. Tomorrow we go on the luge
And the gondola ride, fun
Then quad bikes in the afternoon, Which i'm looking forward to
Honestly? It didn't change anything
You look ex-
I look great
You look fine
You just got a bit more of a line to your beard
Like that’s about it. Sammy, yea you look fine
Show me your face Wally? Aw yea bit dusty
WoW
Yanow we-we’re a bit.. Bit uh.. Muddy
Frank i- Frank is truly living up to his heritage
(scoffs) Witchetty grubs for tea, tell ya what
Dodsley.. Can you tell us what you’re doing?
I failed
Ya failed?
Trying to catch a Natu
Trying to catch a natu?.. He’s playing Pokémon go, what a nerd
What kind of nerd would play Pokémon go
When you’re on holiday? Like.. really?
It’s just me n’ Dodsley, for this part
We’re goin for a walk down Queenstown. Now behd, good soize
This is the lovely queenstown
We’re goin on that later today
Yea, see the gondola over there, in that little
Crack between the trees?
We do the luge on the way down
Walking around, uh catching Pokémon. And gettin Pokéstops
Because that’s what you do when you’re on holiday
Goin on tours yo-you just play Pokémon
C’mon fight this Pokémon bro. Dodsleys winnin over there
I won
He won?
I beat team rocket
Hell yea
Have you ever been in a gondola before?
Nah I havnt
Ever?
Ever. Oh she high up!
Cause I feel like shit, cause we just did quad biking and
everything’s sore and i’m tired and now i’ve just eaten
And now i’m sorta full and I just wanna lie down
I’m more mentally exhausted than anything
Yea mentally exhausted the word
Can’t believe the Queen actually lives here
Fuckin hell..
The New Zealand queen
There was an earthquake that like split the land
And then it like just the water just sunk deep down
Oww
Here we go. So we are there
Wow
And it looks like we gotta, walk down a bit, Chair lift up
Felt pretty unsafe on that one
Yea right!
See one of the- the corner with the fuckin bumps
My ARSE HOLE
Warn you, I tried to warn you
But you were already going over it
By the time I turned around heheheh
I’ll push ya Sammy don’t worry
C’mon Sam work with me a little, push on the side
Here ya ready? Ready?
See ya Dods
You actually enjoy Christmas music?
In your own time?
Yea
That’s amazing
I’ll literally start watching it 3 months before christmas
Oh my god
Guys there's a train! Here comes.. Toot toot
In Ferg we trust, since 2000
That is fuckin heav-ey. Thats awesome
That is, that is the end of today. that..
Imma, imma go into comatose after this bad boy. Good night.
See guys, ya made it, well done Wally, good job
Seeya, nice to meetcha
If you put them on the right way
Ohmygod, Amazing.
Literally how, this is like- (Gasm)
(Gasm)
Push!
Wow, okay it did it did it did
Ah shit WOW
Off roadin, niew
Just go for it! Think light thoughts..
Haha! It works, It works!
Are you fuckin Snappin it? Are you.. Fuckin?
Ok, Hi!
Do it, Aw..
Aw, That was crap.
I’m gonna pause mine
Hello, i’ll get out of the way
Now, we’ve got a criminal here with a mobile phone
Because of the microchip on my body
Against my free will, he had a mocking grin
Well, of course I always get that
Now you see, because of the microchip he knew I was coming here
(inaudible) Criminal with a mocking grin,
Who has no right to have a lime scooter
(Inaudible) You see this is what I mean about criminals,
That, torment their victims who have a microchip
On their body against their free will. He’s got a very nasty evil mocking grin
Now he’s not the first criminal, but the problem with microchips
when they're on their victims against their free will, and, you should see his
Evil mocking grin HE KNEW I was about to come here
Here he’s still here! And he shouldn't have a lime scooter where other
people could trip over. Now i’ve got to wait patiently for him to leave the park-
You ready to go?
Yeah I'm ready to go.
What do we do man I’m shaking in my boosts I can't contain my confusion
Honestly don’t care
Kill me
What are we gonna do?
Go to the check-in counters
Where you will be processed for tomorrow afternoon's flight
(Crowd groans)
We got a whole extra night boys
But where are we gonna stay?
Yea..
What is this?!
(Manly groans)
We just spent half an hour waiting in line like Jeesus
Yea alright
I WANNA DIE HUH?
Ohhh?
Jesus christ Dodsley they’re children
What the fuck was that?
Well this is bougy
Hehey not behehed
Holy shit
What a wack kitchen though
HOLY FUCK
That a big arse shower? noice
Big arse bed, my god. And then you can see the airport, that’s pretty cool
This is actually the way to end this trip
Previously on the airport
If we have to stay another in that hotel I won't be happy
Ohhh boy
I wanna go home
I want a day 7 of New Zealand
I don’t, I wanna go home
...go home
I want this to be over
...go Home..
Like the the ho-motel hotel was nice but, you know
Nearly there boys
Nearly there
It’s happening
It's happening
Stay fuckin calm